Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Personalities [includes color photographs], circa 1923 - 1970s; 1 (Box 1555)
    - Movie Birthday: New York: A birthday cake marks the first year of Broadway run for one of the newest screen techniques. Fred Waller, (center), inventor of Cinerama, is flanked by Hazard Reeves (left), who developed the stereophonic sound used in the multi-dimensional medium, and Lowell Thomas, who was instrumental in producing the film, at cake-cutting ceremonies. 9/29/53, 14
    - Verso: Movie Birthday: New York: A birthday cake marks the first year of Broadway run for one of the newest screen techniques. Fred Waller, (center), inventor of Cinerama, is flanked by Hazard Reeves (left), who developed the stereophonic sound used in the multi-dimensional medium, and Lowell Thomas, who was instrumental in producing the film, at cake-cutting ceremonies. 9/29/53, 14-verso
    - Count Felix von Luckner (the "Sea Devil" of World War I) with LT Jr. and L.T. Sr., 15
    - Verso: Count Felix von Luckner (the "Sea Devil" of World War I) with LT Jr. and L.T. Sr., 15-verso
    - L.T. and Ex-Governor Jas. Cox of Ohio, and a crowd of Dayton business men. About 1923, 16
    - Verso: L.T. and Ex-Governor Jas. Cox of Ohio, and a crowd of Dayton business men. About 1923, 16-verso
    - L.T. David Sarnoff of R.C.A., and Frederick R. Kappel former Chairman of AT&T, 17
    - Verso: L.T. David Sarnoff of R.C.A., and Frederick R. Kappel former Chairman of AT&T, 17-verso
    - Chicago Press Veterans Tenth Annual Dinner, LaSalle Hotel, Chicago, December 4, 1948 The two speakers were the newly elected Governor Adlai Stevenson, second from left, and LT second from right. Sitting beside LT his one time famous City Editor, Richard J. Finnegan. John Delaney of the Chicago Daily News presiding., 18
    - Verso: Chicago Press Veterans Tenth Annual Dinner, LaSalle Hotel, Chicago, December 4, 1948 The two speakers were the newly elected Governor Adlai Stevenson, second from left, and LT second from right. Sitting beside LT his one time famous City Editor, Richard J. Finnegan. John Delaney of the Chicago Daily News presiding., 18-verso
    - Economist Milton Friedman, 19
    - Verso: Economist Milton Friedman, 19-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a man holding a Newsweek magazine], 20
    - [Lowell Thomas delivering a speech at a banquet], 21
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with two men], 22
    - [Three people sitting at a banquet table], 23
    - [Lowell Thomas surrounded by a group of people], 24
    - [Lowell Thomas and three other men talking at an event], 25
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a man], 26
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man], 27
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man in an art gallery], 28
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a man], 29
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man standing in front of a lake and mountains], 30
    - [A man presenting Lowell Thomas with a plaque], 31
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man standing in front of the American flag holding an award], 32
  - Subject files: Personalities, 1930s - 1970s; 2 (Box 1555)
    - Left to Right - Joseph L. Beesley, Sen. V.P., Lowell Thomas, Melville P. Dickenson, Sen. V.P., 1
    - Verso: Left to Right - Joseph L. Beesley, Sen. V.P., Lowell Thomas, Melville P. Dickenson, Sen. V.P., 1-verso
    - Left to right - Joseph L. Beesley, Senior V.P., Charles R. Corcoran, V.P., Melville P. Dickenson, Senior V.P., Lowell Thomas, 2
    - Verso: Left to right - Joseph L. Beesley, Senior V.P., Charles R. Corcoran, V.P., Melville P. Dickenson, Senior V.P., Lowell Thomas, 2-verso
    - L.T., Ted Mack, Dan Moore, 3
    - Verso: L.T., Ted Mack, Dan Moore, 3-verso
    - LT - Sen. Saltonstall, 4
    - Verso: LT - Sen. Saltonstall, 4-verso
    - Lowell Thomas Jr., Admiral George Edwards, Lowell Thomas Sr., 5
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas Jr., Admiral George Edwards, Lowell Thomas Sr., 5-verso
    - April 16, 1970; Grand Ballroom, Conrad Hilton Hotel; Left to right: Pres. Columbia Broadcasting System, Dinah Shore, Mike Hogan, Lowell Thomas, 6
    - Verso: April 16, 1970; Grand Ballroom, Conrad Hilton Hotel; Left to right: Pres. Columbia Broadcasting System, Dinah Shore, Mike Hogan, Lowell Thomas, 6-verso
    - [Dinah Shore, Lowell Thomas at podium], 7
    - ? Ask Sam Pryor who, 8
    - Verso: ? Ask Sam Pryor who, 8-verso
    - LT and two General Motors Executives; Left: Louis C. Goad and right, Edward N. Cole, 9
    - Verso: LT and two General Motors Executives; Left: Louis C. Goad and right, Edward N. Cole, 9-verso
    - Ex. V.P. of GM Ll. "Chief" Goad [?] and Ed Cole [3 copies], 10
    - Verso: Ex. V.P. of GM Ll. "Chief" Goad [?] and Ed Cole, 10-verso
    - LT crowning Miss Kathleen Gray, Queen of the Washington, D.C. Auto show, 11
    - Verso: LT crowning Miss Kathleen Gray, Queen of the Washington, D.C. Auto show, 11-verso
    - Note: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Maurice J. Murphy concerning photograph taken at Auto Show (2.11)], 12
    - Boston Broadcast with Gov. Saltonstall, Chancellor of Univ. Mexico and the Peruvian gentleman who is Pres. of Rotary International, 13
    - Verso: Boston Broadcast with Gov. Saltonstall, Chancellor of Univ. Mexico and the Peruvian gentleman who is Pres. of Rotary International, 13-verso
    - Left to Right - Moyer, Arkedis, Feeley, Thomas, Knudsen, 14
    - Verso: Left to Right - Moyer, Arkedis, Feeley, Thomas, Knudsen, 14-verso
    - on right Gov. of Illinois - 1975 - Gov. Daniel Walker, middle - one of heads of Junior Achievement Int. - Richard Maxwell, LT - left; In back, wearing glasses is W. F. "Al" Rockwell, Jr., 15
    - Verso: on right Gov. of Illinois - 1975 - Gov. Daniel Walker, middle - one of heads of Junior Achievement Int. - Richard Maxwell, LT - left; In back, wearing glasses is W. F. "Al" Rockwell, Jr., 15-verso
    - General "Larry" Kuter, chief of the Continental Defense Command; Mr. and Mrs. Joe Binns, LT, 16
    - Verso: General "Larry" Kuter, chief of the Continental Defense Command; Mr. and Mrs. Joe Binns, LT, 16-verso
    - [General "Larry" Kuter, chief of the Continental Defense Command; Mr. and Mrs. Joe Binns, LT], 17
    - [Luncheon at which Herbert Hoover was presented the gold medal of the City of New York from Mayor Wagner, 1959], 18
    - Note: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Peter Grim concerning photograph of Luncheon at which Herbert Hoover was presented the gold medal of the City of New York from Mayor Wagner, 1959], 19
    - Maury H.B. Paul, famous society writer "Cholly Knickerbocker" of the New York Journal American and other Hearst Publications, in conversation with George McManus, prominent cartoonist of "Jiggs and Maggie" fame, and Lowell Thomas, news commentator, author and lecturer, looks on, 20
    - Note: Maury H.B. Paul, famous society writer "Cholly Knickerbocker" of the New York Journal American and other Hearst Publications, in conversation with George McManus, prominent cartoonist of "Jiggs and Maggie" fame, and Lowell Thomas, news commentator, author and lecturer, looks on, 21
    - Harlow Curtice, former Chairman of the Board of General Motors, LT and Mr. Charles S. Mott, Board of Directors of General Motors, 22
    - Verso: Harlow Curtice, former Chairman of the Board of General Motors, LT and Mr. Charles S. Mott, Board of Directors of General Motors, 22-verso
    - Mr. [Charles S]. Mott, [Board of Directors of General Motors], 23
    - Verso: Mr. [Charles S]. Mott, [Board of Directors of General Motors], 23-verso
    - [Mr. [Charles S]. Mott [center], [Board of Directors of General Motors]], 24
    - [Lowell Thomas with two men in front of an airplane], 25
    - [Lowell Tomas and two men looking at a sheet of metal], 26
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with two men at an event], 27
    - [Lowell Thomas standing outside with a man], 28
    - [Lowell Thomas holding the microphone for a man], 29
    - [Lowell Thomas with two other men], 30
    - [Lowell Thomas and two men outside], 31
    - [Lowell Thomas and a young man standing outside], 32
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man talking about a pamphlet], 33
  - Subject files: Personalities [includes color photograph], 1930s - 1970s; 3 (Box 1555)
    - Mrs. Adrien [Anean?], Peter Grimm and LT., 1
    - Verso: Mrs. Adrien [Anean?], Peter Grimm and LT., 1-verso
    - Chuck Skinner - Olds.; General Motors Motorama, New York - 1956; Note: Chuck Skinner - for many years the head of Olds?., 2
    - Verso: Chuck Skinner - Olds.; General Motors Motorama, New York - 1956, 2-verso
    - Note: Chuck Skinner - for many years the head of Olds?., 3
    - Allan Hoover, Mrs. Allan Hoover, 4
    - Verso: Allan Hoover, Mrs. Allan Hoover, 4-verso
    - Mr. Allan Hoover, 5
    - Verso: Mr. Allan Hoover, 5-verso
    - Joe Binns, 6
    - Verso: Joe Binns, 6-verso
    - Mr. and Mrs. Wm. I. Nichols, 7
    - Verso: Mr. and Mrs. Wm. I. Nichols, 7-verso
    - Mr. Wm. I. Nichols, 8
    - Verso: Mr. Wm. I. Nichols, 8-verso
    - Grand Prize Winner Judges of the Newspaper National Snapshot Awards Contest look over the entry which won the grand prize after the judging Oct. 14 in Washington - that of H.S. Shields of Columbus, O. Left to right: Charles Phelps, Jr., President, Photographic Society of America; Yousuf Karsh, Photographer, and Lowell Thomas, commentator, holding the prize picture; and Edwin L. Wisherd, of National Geographic Society. Vancouver Province 10-44-47, 9
    - Verso: Grand Prize Winner Judges of the Newspaper National Snapshot Awards Contest look over the entry which won the grand prize after the judging Oct. 14 in Washington - that of H.S. Shields of Columbus, O. Left to right: Charles Phelps, Jr., President, Photographic Society of America; Yousuf Karsh, Photographer, and Lowell Thomas, commentator, holding the prize picture; and Edwin L. Wisherd, of National Geographic Society. Vancouver Province 10-44-47, 9-verso
    - Lowell Thomas Honored by his college fraternity Lowell Thomas, famous author, news commentator and world traveler, smiles happily after receiving the 1938 Man of the Year Award from his college fraternity, Kappa Sigma. The presentation was made Friday evening, December 9, before 300 members of the fraternity at the Merchants and Manufacturers Club in Chicago. Hill Blackett, Chicago and New York advertising agency president, made the presentation, and Wesley W. Kergan, San Francisco attorney and Worthy Grand Scribe of Kappa Sigma, registers an expression of satisfaction as the fraternity has singled out another of its members for honor. Thomas was given this award after nation-wide balloting for his iron man feats as an author, adventurer and consistent accuracy in news commentating for over eight years on radio and screen., 10
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas Honored by his college fraternity Lowell Thomas, famous author, news commentator and world traveler, smiles happily after receiving the 1938 Man of the Year Award from his college fraternity, Kappa Sigma. The presentation was made Friday evening, December 9, before 300 members of the fraternity at the Merchants and Manufacturers Club in Chicago. Hill Blackett, Chicago and New York advertising agency president, made the presentation, and Wesley W. Kergan, San Francisco attorney and Worthy Grand Scribe of Kappa Sigma, registers an expression of satisfaction as the fraternity has singled out another of its members for honor. Thomas was given this award after nation-wide balloting for his iron man feats as an author, adventurer and consistent accuracy in news commentating for over eight years on radio and screen., 10-verso
    - L to R: John Berry (foreground), (woman behind), Henry J. Taylor, Lowell Thomas, William S. Huff (seated), 11
    - Verso: L to R: John Berry (foreground), (woman behind), Henry J. Taylor, Lowell Thomas, William S. Huff (seated), 11-verso
    - L to R: Ferris Mack, Lanny Ross, Lowell Thomas, 12
    - Verso: L to R: Ferris Mack, Lanny Ross, Lowell Thomas, 12-verso
    - L. Garrett, VP of GM, 13
    - Verso: L. Garrett, VP of GM, 13-verso
    - [L. Garrett, VP of GM], 14
    - Will Rogers Jr., Geo. Putnam, 15
    - Verso: Will Rogers Jr., Geo. Putnam, 15-verso
    - Paul Sorvino, actor/singer, 16
    - Verso: Paul Sorvino, actor/singer, 16-verso
    - Paul Sorvino, actor/singer, 17
    - Verso: Paul Sorvino, actor/singer, 17-verso
    - On the left Pat Winthrow, head of a Charleston, West Virginia Mission. His main work was rescuing alcoholics, rehabilitating drunken bums., 18
    - Verso: On the left Pat Winthrow, head of a Charleston, West Virginia Mission. His main work was rescuing alcoholics, rehabilitating drunken bums., 18-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas delivering a speech at an Advertising of New York event], 19
    - [Five men standing on a ship], 20
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a group of men on a ship], 21
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting at a banquet table], 22
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting at a banquet table], 23
    - [Lowell Thomas going up to a podium], 24
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with three men], 25
    - [Lowell Thomas speakign with a man], 26
    - [Lowell Thomas talking to Dan Moore (?) and another man], 27
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man], 28
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with two women and a man], 29
    - [Lowell Thomas talking with two women and a man], 30
    - [Lowell Thomas standing in front of a n NCA plane with three other people], 31
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with a man and two women at an event], 32
    - [Lowell Thomas signing his book, "Lowell Thomas' Book of the High Mountains"], 33
  - Subject files: Personalities [includes color photographs], 1930s - 1970s; 4 (Box 1555)
    - Dan Moore, 1
    - Verso: Dan Moore, 1-verso
    - J. Charmoz, 2
    - Verso: J. Charmoz, 2-verso
    - In Lansing, Michigan, at the celebration of the Centennial of Farm Mechanization, Lowell Thomas (right), famous World traveler and Delco Battery newscaster, helps Alexander Tulupnikov, member of the Russian farm delegation visiting United States, with his "coffee break." Thomas, came from New York to do his evening newscast from the campus of Michigan State University, where the celebration took place, 3
    - Verso: In Lansing, Michigan, at the celebration of the Centennial of Farm Mechanization, Lowell Thomas (right), famous World traveler and Delco Battery newscaster, helps Alexander Tulupnikov, member of the Russian farm delegation visiting United States, with his "coffee break." Thomas, came from New York to do his evening newscast from the campus of Michigan State University, where the celebration took place, 3-verso
    - Lowell Thomas and Melville P. Dickenson, Sen. V.P., 4
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas and Melville P. Dickenson, Sen. V.P., 4-verso
    - Left to right: Lowell Thomas, Melville P. Dickenson, Senior V.P., Charles R. Corcoran, V.P., Joseph L. Beesley, Senior V.P., 5
    - Verso: Left to right: Lowell Thomas, Melville P. Dickenson, Senior V.P., Charles R. Corcoran, V.P., Joseph L. Beesley, Senior V.P., 5-verso
    - Lila Acheson Wallace and DeWitt Wallace - Reader's Digest; Mr. and Mrs. Dewitt Wallace, 6
    - Verso: Lila Acheson Wallace and DeWitt Wallace - Reader's Digest; Mr. and Mrs. Dewitt Wallace, 6-verso
    - Ed Cole of General Motors, 7
    - Note: Ed Cole of General Motors, 8
    - HACK MILLER; This looks like two old members of Bohemian Grove who, after the 1919 session, didn't ever go home - but lingered in the woods, 9
    - Note: HACK MILLER; This looks like two old members of Bohemian Grove who, after the 1919 session, didn't ever go home - but lingered in the woods, 10
    - June 1976 Bob Dunne, J. Walter Thompson, 11
    - Verso: June 1976 Bob Dunne, J. Walter Thompson, 11-verso
    - 10-15-73; Caption: To you Lowell, a regular guy who always thinks of the other person [signed] Frank Domeracki, 12
    - Verso: 10-15-73; Caption: To you Lowell, a regular guy who always thinks of the other person [signed] Frank Domeracki, 12-verso
    - With Colonel Jack Allard of General Doolittle's staff, 13
    - Verso: With Colonel Jack Allard of General Doolittle's staff, 13-verso
    - Melville P. Dickenson, Senior V.P. and Lowell Thomas, 14
    - Verso: Melville P. Dickenson, Senior V.P. and Lowell Thomas, 14-verso
    - Caption: For my friend Lowell Thomas [signed] John H. [?], 15
    - West Branch, Iowa, 16
    - Verso: West Branch, Iowa, 16-verso
    - Sheraton Hotel, Bust Award [Lowell Thomas, center, Jack Anderson, right], 17
    - Note: Sheraton Hotel, Bust Award [Lowell Thomas, center, Jack Anderson, right], 18
    - Tom Burke; One time manager of the LT speaking tour of America and later head of the National Safety Council, 19
    - Verso: Tom Burke; One time manager of the LT speaking tour of America and later head of the National Safety Council, 19-verso
    - Mrs S - Gene Stratemeyer - Mrs. Doolittle, 20
    - Verso: Mrs S - Gene Stratemeyer - Mrs. Doolittle, 20-verso
    - Dr. Geo. Crile Jr. [Mrs. Marianna Thomas, right], 21
    - Verso: Dr. Geo. Crile Jr. [Mrs. Marianna Thomas, right], 21-verso
    - Withers, Skinner, 22
    - Verso: Withers, Skinner, 22-verso
    - Caption: Dick Bass, Harold Byrd, Stuart Hunt, John Murchison, Lowell Thomas, 23
    - Caption: Neil Mallon, Harold Byrd, Dick Hauserman, Lowell Thomas, 24
    - Caption: Dick Hauserman, Harold Byrd, Allen Humphrey, Lowell Thomas, 25
    - Caption: Lowell, Happiness is a warm friend and a long run on the slopes - Always, [signed] Hugh [O'Brien], 26
    - Ambassador Richard C. Patterson, Grimm, Mrs. Patterson, Mrs. T, Fred Clark, Mrs. Diana Clark, L.T., Mrs. Nathan, Mrs. Grimm, Robert Moses, 27
    - Note: Ambassador Richard C. Patterson, Grimm, Mrs. Patterson, Mrs. T, Fred Clark, Mrs. Diana Clark, L.T., Mrs. Nathan, Mrs. Grimm, Robert Moses, 28
    - LOWELL THOMAS RECEIVES AMERICAN LEGION PUBLIC RELATIONS AWARD - Veteran reporter and commentator Lowell Thomas is presented the 1972 American Legion National Commander's Public Relations Award by National Commander John H. Geiger, of Des Plaines, Ill., at the Legion's annual Public Relations Luncheon held March 1, 1972. Newsman Thomas was cited for "his pioneering efforts in the audio visual field as a commentator and lecturer on our world" and for bringing to the people of the world "a greater understanding of diverse lands and cultures." The Legion's Public Relations Luncheon was held in conjunction with the organization's 12th annual Washington Conference, February 27 - March 3. L to R: James Rowley, Director, U.S. Secret Service; Lowell Thomas, 29
    - Verso: LOWELL THOMAS RECEIVES AMERICAN LEGION PUBLIC RELATIONS AWARD - Veteran reporter and commentator Lowell Thomas is presented the 1972 American Legion National Commander's Public Relations Award by National Commander John H. Geiger, of Des Plaines, Ill., at the Legion's annual Public Relations Luncheon held March 1, 1972. Newsman Thomas was cited for "his pioneering efforts in the audio visual field as a commentator and lecturer on our world" and for bringing to the people of the world "a greater understanding of diverse lands and cultures." The Legion's Public Relations Luncheon was held in conjunction with the organization's 12th annual Washington Conference, February 27 - March 3. L to R: James Rowley, Director, U.S. Secret Service; Lowell Thomas, 29-verso
    - L.T. and Ed Cole, Pres. Of Gen Motors. G.M. sponsored LT for 20 yrs on the air - longest sponsor-talent tie ever., 30
    - Verso: L.T. and Ed Cole, Pres. Of Gen Motors. G.M. sponsored LT for 20 yrs on the air - longest sponsor-talent tie ever., 30-verso
    - With Dr. Leonard Carmichael, Farmer head of the Smithsonian, 31
    - Verso: With Dr. Leonard Carmichael, Farmer head of the Smithsonian, 31-verso
    - L.T. talks with a welder at New England Shipbuilding Corp., Portland, Me., during war, 32
    - Verso: L.T. talks with a welder at New England Shipbuilding Corp., Portland, Me., during war, 32-verso
    - Colonial Penn, Pres. of Phila Ins. Co.??, 33
    - Verso: Colonial Penn, Pres. of Phila Ins. Co.??, 33-verso
    - [Herbert Hoover, center, Lowell Thomas, right], 34
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man standing in a photograph gallery], 35
  - Subject files: Personalities [includes color photographs], 1930s - 1970s; 5 (Box 1555)
    - Myron Ehrenberg, 1
    - Verso: Myron Ehrenberg, 1-verso
    - Richards - voice of Mormons, 2
    - Verso: Richards - voice of Mormons, 2-verso
    - Caption: To a great Alaskan friend, [signed] Walter J. Hickel, 3
    - Caption: To a great "Alaskan B[?]", [signed] Walter J. Hickel, Gov. of Alaska, 4
    - Malcolm Forbes, 5
    - Verso: Malcolm Forbes, 5-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas with Jawaharlal Nehru], 6
    - General [Alexander] Haig, DT May 74, 7
    - Verso: General [Alexander] Haig, DT May 74, 7-verso
    - General Alex Haig and LT at a Washington, D.C. banquet. They are old friends - since Haig was a lieutenant, 8
    - Verso: General Alex Haig and LT at a Washington, D.C. banquet. They are old friends - since Haig was a lieutenant, 8-verso
    - LT and Jack Anderson, left, Danny Kaye on right. LT was giving Danny an award, 9
    - Verso: LT and Jack Anderson, left, Danny Kaye on right. LT was giving Danny an award, 9-verso
    - LT and Chas. "Chuck" Skinner, V.P. of Gen. Motors and head of Olds, 10
    - Verso: LT and Chas. "Chuck" Skinner, V.P. of Gen. Motors and head of Olds, 10-verso
    - Dr. Hobart Van Deusen - Pres., 11
    - Verso: Dr. Hobart Van Deusen - Pres., 11-verso
    - L.T. and Gov. Steve McNichols of Colorado, 12
    - Verso: L.T. and Gov. Steve McNichols of Colorado, 12-verso
    - Gov. Tom Bailey of Mississippi and L.T., 13
    - Verso: Gov. Tom Bailey of Mississippi and L.T., 13-verso
    - Two names in the news, Frontier Airlines' new president, Lewis W. Dymond, (left) and news commentator, author, lecturer and world traveler Lowell Thomas, also a newly-elected member of Frontier's Board of Directors, consulted together in Denver. Under consideration are plans for better air service throughout the airline's 10-state system in the Rocky Mountain West and Midwest, 14
    - Verso: Two names in the news, Frontier Airlines' new president, Lewis W. Dymond, (left) and news commentator, author, lecturer and world traveler Lowell Thomas, also a newly-elected member of Frontier's Board of Directors, consulted together in Denver. Under consideration are plans for better air service throughout the airline's 10-state system in the Rocky Mountain West and Midwest, 14-verso
    - Elena [Whitney?], 15
    - Verso: Elena [Whitney?], 15-verso
    - Isaac Asimov, 16
    - Verso: Isaac Asimov, 16-verso
    - Frank Farrell, columnist; Sigmund Spaeth, authority on music, coach and Prof. at Princeton [Lowell Thomas, right], 17
    - Verso: Frank Farrell, columnist; Sigmund Spaeth, authority on music, coach and Prof. at Princeton [Lowell Thomas, right], 17-verso
    - George Champion, Chase Manhattan Bank, Former Chairman, 18
    - Verso: George Champion, Chase Manhattan Bank, Former Chairman, 18-verso
    - Clement Stone, 19
    - Verso: Clement Stone, 19-verso
    - 7/7/76 Governor's Island Greeting Capt. Kjell Thorsen of the CHRISTIAN RADICH, 20
    - Verso: 7/7/76 Governor's Island Greeting Capt. Kjell Thorsen of the CHRISTIAN RADICH, 20-verso
    - G.L. Phillipe, Pres. of General Electic and L.T., 21
    - Verso: G.L. Phillipe, Pres. of General Electic and L.T., 21-verso